gamehourz.com 2014-04-07

# Game Forums

PRIVACY POLICY

_"GameHourz.com never shares individual email addresses with any third parties, including advertisers or partners, without prior consent from our users."_

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of GameHourz.com we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. 

INFORMATION GameHourz.com GATHERS & TRACKS

GameHourz.com gathers two types of information about users: data that users provide through optional, voluntary registration; and data GameHourz.com gathers through tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views and posts throughout GameHourz.com. Such information enables us to better tailor our features and content to users' needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. 

GameHourz.com currently gathers user information in the following processes: 

OPTIONAL REGISTRATION

GameHourz.com offers free, voluntary registration to users. By registering, users can post new messages, and sign-up for automatic email notifications. During registration the user is required to supply information about himself/herself including but not limited to name, a username, password, and email address.

SURVEYS

Occasionally, GameHourz.com conducts user surveys to better understand the needs of our audience in order to improve our features. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party without user's express consent. 

USAGE TRACKING

GameHourz.com tracks user traffic patterns (e.g., which forum sections you visit) throughout GameHourz.com and GameHourz.com. This information may be used to help personalize the GameHourz.com service or target advertising. GameHourz.com also breaks down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). 

COOKIES

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. GameHourz.com uses cookies to allow automatic logins, and to track usage traffic patterns (as described above). 

When you register, GameHourz.com uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site. Cookies also enable you to enter GameHourz.com as a member without having to log on each time. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to view forums on GameHourz.com. However, you do need cookies to post messages. 

USE OF INFORMATION

GameHourz.com uses any information given by our users to enhance their experience, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on GameHourz.com or to better prepare future features based on the interests of our users. 

GameHourz.com uses your email information to provide more personalized features. At a user's request we will send out emails notifying the user of replies to specific postings. We also provide the option for the user to allow other users to respond to postings directly via their email. GameHourz.com may also send the user email notifications of specific changes to our service. GameHourz.com never shares individual email addresses with any third parties, including advertisers or partners, without prior consent from our users. 

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of GameHourz.com users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. GameHourz.com does not track what messages individual users read, but rather how well each forum or thread or feature performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

GameHourz.com creates aggregrate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. 

SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

GameHourz.com uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and to help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. We do not share individually identifiable information about specific users with any third party without prior consent from the user. GameHourz.com does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly (GameHourz.com will divulge information only as necessary to comply with state, provincial, and federal laws.) 

OPT OUT POLICY

GameHourz.com gives users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include: Opting not to receive our electronic messages, opting not to provide certain optional personal information when registering for an account (see above), and opting not to participate in message posting, which completely alleviates the need to register for an account or to provide identifiable information 

CORRECT/UPDATED POLICY

GameHourz.com offers users the ability to correct or change the information collected during registration process (see above). Users may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. Users may also delete their account at any time by contacting us (all profile information, excluding already posted messages, will be eliminated from our records). Users who are experiencing problems or who have any questions about how our services work can contact us as well.
